investingnews.com 2016-11-20

# Privacy Policy | Investing News Network

This website is part of the Investing News Network published by Dig Media Inc.

  * Overview
  * Contact Information
  * Information Collected
  * Ad Server
  * Information Use
  * Remarketing
  * Future Use
  * Accessing Your Data
  * Security
  * Your Acceptance of These Terms

## Overview

INN’s mission is to be the world’s number one source of independent, unbiased news and education helping investors realized their financial goals. We also strive to be internationally respected for our integrity, our people and our commitment to excellence. Therefore, we are very concerned with the privacy rights of our audience and are committed to protecting the information collected about you.We have taken extensive measures to protect the confidentiality of your personal information and to protect your data from misuse and unauthorized access or disclosure. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, Dig Media cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

Our postal address is

L200 – 560 Beatty Street,

Vancouver, BC V6B 2L3

We can be reached via e-mail at info@digmediasolutions.com or telephone at +1-604-688-8231

## Information Collected

For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

We collect information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number.

The information we collect is used to notify visitors about updates to our website, shared with other reputable organizations to help them contact visitors for marketing purposes.

With respect to cookies: When you visit our websites, we send one or more cookies, a small file containing a string of characters, to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser during your visit. We use these cookies to maintain your connection as you move from page to page, and to ensure anything you submit, such as a comment or a form, is not rejected. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address.

## Ad Server

With respect to Ad Servers:

Other third-party companies which place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of their cookies or other tracking technologies, which may include delivering targeted advertisements and marketing messages based upon the third party websites that you visit, or other purposes. We cannot control this collection of information and are not responsible for the privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices of these third party advertisers. You should contact these third party advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect from you. Google-DoubleClick DFP is our third party ad server. If you would like to know more about their information gathering practices and opt-out procedures, please see [Google ad policies](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

Also, if you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see [NAI Opt-out Options](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

## Information Use

We only share personal information with other companies or individuals outside of the cases outlined above in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Dig Media, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually.

We may remarket your information. Remarketing is a way for us to connect with users, based upon your past interactions with INN websites. Third-party marketing vendors may be hired by INN to perform remarketing services. As a result, third-party vendors, including Google, may show INN ads on sites on the internet. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to INN websites.

To opt out of customized Google Display Network ads click [here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb). To find out more about how Google uses any data it collects please visit <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.  
Any information collected is used only for remarketing purposes and will not be used by them for any other purpose.

## Future Use

From time to time, we may use visitor information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.

## Accessing Your Data

Please contact us at the address above for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to communications that the visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them.

Visitors can access this information by e-mailing us at the above address.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information.

Visitors can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address.

## Security

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

## Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this site, or by submitting personal information to us, you signify your agreement to Dig Media’s Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. From time to time we may change or update our piracy policies. It is your responsibility to check back regularly to inform yourself of such changes. Your continued use of this or any Dig Media website following the posting of changes to these terms will be deemed as your acceptance of those changes.

The foregoing policies are in effect as of August 1, 2012. Dig media reserves the right to change this policy statement at any time by posting the revised policy to this website. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

##### Enter Your Log In Credentials

×

## Privacy & Legal Policy

This website is part of the Investing News Network published by Dig Media Inc.

  * Overview
  * Contact Information
  * Information Collected
  * Ad Server
  * Information Use
  * Remarketing
  * Future Use
  * Accessing Your Data
  * Security
  * Your Acceptance of These Terms

## Overview

INN's mission is to be the world's number one source of independent, unbiased news and education helping investors realized their financial goals. We also strive to be internationally respected for our integrity, our people and our commitment to excellence. Therefore, we are very concerned with the privacy rights of our audience and are committed to protecting the information collected about you.We have taken extensive measures to protect the confidentiality of your personal information and to protect your data from misuse and unauthorized access or disclosure. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, Dig Media cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

Our postal address is

L200 - 560 Beatty Street,

Vancouver, BC V6B 2L3

We can be reached via e-mail at info@digmediasolutions.com or telephone at +1-604-688-8231

## Information Collected

For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

We collect information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number.

The information we collect is used to notify visitors about updates to our website, shared with other reputable organizations to help them contact visitors for marketing purposes.

With respect to cookies: When you visit our websites, we send one or more cookies, a small file containing a string of characters, to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser during your visit. We use these cookies to maintain your connection as you move from page to page, and to ensure anything you submit, such as a comment or a form, is not rejected. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address.

## Ad Server

With respect to Ad Servers:

Other third-party companies which place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of their cookies or other tracking technologies, which may include delivering targeted advertisements and marketing messages based upon the third party websites that you visit, or other purposes. We cannot control this collection of information and are not responsible for the privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices of these third party advertisers. You should contact these third party advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect from you. Google-DoubleClick DFP is our third party ad server. If you would like to know more about their information gathering practices and opt-out procedures, please see [Google ad policies](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

Also, if you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see [NAI Opt-out Options](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

## Information Use

We only share personal information with other companies or individuals outside of the cases outlined above in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Dig Media, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually.

We may remarket your information. Remarketing is a way for us to connect with users, based upon your past interactions with INN websites. Third-party marketing vendors may be hired by INN to perform remarketing services. As a result, third-party vendors, including Google, may show INN ads on sites on the internet. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to INN websites.

To opt out of customized Google Display Network ads click [here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb). To find out more about how Google uses any data it collects please visit <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.  
Any information collected is used only for remarketing purposes and will not be used by them for any other purpose.

## Future Use

From time to time, we may use visitor information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.

## Accessing Your Data

Please contact us at the address above for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to communications that the visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them.

Visitors can access this information by e-mailing us at the above address.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information.

Visitors can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address.

## Security

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

## Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this site, or by submitting personal information to us, you signify your agreement to Dig Media's Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. From time to time we may change or update our piracy policies. It is your responsibility to check back regularly to inform yourself of such changes. Your continued use of this or any Dig Media website following the posting of changes to these terms will be deemed as your acceptance of those changes.

The foregoing policies are in effect as of August 1, 2012. Dig media reserves the right to change this policy statement at any time by posting the revised policy to this website. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

×
